hi I'm Olivia I'm here in San Diego for
directions North America a Microsoft
conference I'm one of the new hires with
the res skill program so let's go take a
look around come on I was the first
North American new hire for the res
skill program I have an industrial
engineering background but I figured I
could use a good challenge in Tech so I
went through the program and now I'm a
junior consultant with clients first so
here I am in the beginning it was a lot
of information to absorb all at once but
the more I got used to it the more I
learned and the more I applied the
information I was learning the easier it
became the more things started to make
sense I was afraid at first that I would
never be able to remember everything
that I was learning um especially since
there's so much to know about business
Central um and I was also afraid that I
wouldn't be good at it with my
background but the more I got into it
the more I became comfortable and the
more I realized that it's all learning
experience
and nobody is proficient in business
Central in every area we all learn
something new every day and everyday is
a learning
experience the res skill program starts
with a series of modules where you learn
all the information that you need to get
started in business Central but it
doesn't stop there you also learn all
the professional skills you need to be a
successful consultant you learn how to
interact with clients and there's
sessions with other people in the
program who are also going going through
the same thing that you are so you can
grow as a community together and learn
as a community together and it's just a
fantastic experience to learn a new
skill and especially if you're looking
for a challenge after 9 months in the
res skill program I've been introduced
to a large community of like-minded
individuals who have also gone through
the same program that I have and it's
created a great community that we can
lean on each other when we need some
help or when we have questions and it's
been so cool to interact with people
from all over the world who are
interested in the same thing I
am events like these allow us to meet
the people that we've spoke with
virtually but have never met in person
and interact with them as well as
meeting new people in various different
areas of this community and get new
contacts in different companies that can
help us with future implementation it's
all about the networking
while at directions I plan on learning
as much as I can and I'm also going to
be speaking at a couple sessions one for
the women in Dynamics and the other
talking about the res skill program so
I'm going to go get my
badge hello
[Music]
it was such a great experience I learned
so much and was exposed so much um I was
able to meet a ton of new people whove
been in this career for decades and got
a lot of really great advice so it was
it was fantastic being on stage was so
nerve-wracking but that's the whole
reason I did it I chose to put myself
out of my comfort zone and um I'm really
glad that I did and I'm proud of the
answers that I gave the future holds a
lot of continuous learning I'm so
excited to see where I can take the
knowledge I already have and how much
knowledge I can gain and also looking
forward to seeing my first project that
I'll be able to see start to finish go
live uh hopefully that'll be within the
next 6 months to a year and so I'm
really looking forward to seeing that
happen
[Music]